

Max Vome

463 Sanders Farm Lane, Charleston, SC 29492

Driven Professional

- (843) 864-1432
- mv343203@gmail.com
- Personal Website
- LinkedIn Profile
- % GitHub Profile

Check out my website and GitHub account for more examples of my direct work/studies.

CONTINUOUS LEARNING

CodeCademy Pro 2018-2019

Career Path Computer Science

Coursera 2019-2020

Programming Foundations with JavaScript, HTML and CSS Java Programming: Principles of Software Design Java Programming: Arrays, Lists and Structured Data Python: Using Databases with Python Python: Data Structures

Udemy

2019-2021

Python – Build 10 Real World Applications
REACT – Complete React Dev. (Hooks & Redux)
MySQL – Data Analytics & Business Intelligence
Java – Spring Framework 5: Beginner to Guru
Django 3 – Full Stack Websites w/Python

AWS 2021

AWS Ramp-Up Guide: Developer prescriptive path

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science Environmental Health Science Ohio University

ABOUT ME

Technology intrigued professional seeking to switch career paths. Through utilization of Coursera, Udemy, CodeCademy and AWS, I've built knowledge & skills in coding within Java, Python, SQL & REACT.

Collaborative Environmental, Health and Safety Manager with 10+ years of experience. Looking for a challenging developmental position in software engineering. Passionate about continuous learning, driven and a fast learner with excellent communication, and leadership skills.

EXPERIENCE

Environmental, Health, Safety and Security Manager

KION North America Inc. / Summerville, SC / March 2015- Present

- Created and implemented web-based application for HSE related matters (Python – Flask & Google Cloud Platform)
- Implemented and manage onsite fire, security and access control systems.
- Project Manager for installation of a \$1.5 MM capital solar panel project.
- Implemented ISO 14001 and 45001 EHSMS certifications and responsible for the continuation of surveillance audits.
- Responsibility for training, DOT compliance and creating a culture of safety.

Environmental, Health and Safety Manager

Saint-Gobain ADFORS / North Charleston, SC & Russellville, AL / February 2014-March 2015

- In partnership with IT assisted in developing and testing a web-based application for hazard reporting.
- Multisite responsibility for communication, implementation and reporting for all EHS programs (ISO 14001, WCM).
- Responsible for the design of EHS processes for a \$20MM CAPEX project with over 180 onsite contractors.

Environmental and Safety Engineer

General Dynamics Land Systems – Force Protection / Ladson, SC / October 2011-February 2014

- Created a corrective action system (within SharePoint) in order to streamline company EHSMS non-conformances.
- Lead and coordinated ISO 14001 and implemented OHSAS 18001 EHSMS certifications and responsible for the continuation of surveillance audits.
- Reduced hazardous waste generation offering a cost savings of \$50k